&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，让我们深入到词汇范围，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All right, so let's dig into lexical scope,
让我们看看这段特殊的代码。
let's take a look at this particular code.
这看起来很眼熟
This should look familiar,
这是我们之前做的相同类型的代码。
this is the same kind of code that we were doing before.
在作者的时候，
And at author time,
当我决定将该函数放入函数other Class()中时，请将其放入函数中。
when I decided to put the function ask inside of the function otherClass().
我不可挽回地决定变量引用
I irrevocably decided that the variable reference
将指向第4行声明的变量。
on line 7 is going to point at the variable that was declared on line 4.
换句话说，大理石的颜色是在编译时决定的。
In other words the marble color was decided at compile time.
实际上不是这个查找过程，
It's not actually this look up process,
就像我们在运行时阶段讨论的那样。
like we discussed during the run time phase.
当我在叙述中使用它给你一个概念模型时，我有点撒谎了。
I sort of fibbed when I used that in the narrative to give you a conceptual model.
但不是在运行时它必须说嘿，问的范围，
But it is not the case that at run time it has to say hey, scope of ask,
你听说过这个大理石吗？
have you ever heard of this marble?
嘿，其他课程的范围，你听说过这个大理石吗？
And hey, scope of other class, have you ever heard of this marble?
因为至少这个程序的编写方式，
Because at least the way this program's written,
我们在编译时知道大理石是什么颜色。
we know at compile time what color the marble is.
即使在最坏的情况下，我们也可能
And even in the worst case scenario, where we might for
有些原因不知道编译时的颜色大理石是什么。
some reason not know what the color marble was from the compile time.
我们第一次就会弄明白的，而且
We're gonna figure it out the very first time, and
那么我们就不需要再弄明白了，因为它永远不会改变。
then we don’t need to figure it out ever again, cuz it’s never gonna change.
所以词汇范围实际上是如此的原因之一
So one of the reasons why lexical scope is actually so
流行是因为它是如此的可优化。
popular is because it’s so optimizable.
你可以决定什么时候编辑东西，
This idea that you can decide when you're compiling things,
所有这些变量都是从哪里来的，
where all of those variables come from,
弹珠是什么颜色，我们不需要在运行时弄清楚那些东西。
what color the marbles are, we don’t need to figure that stuff out at runtime.
这就是你应该从词法范围得到的。
That’s what you should get from lexical scope.
帮助我将这些界限留在脑中的方法之一。
One of the ways that helps me keep those boundaries in my head.
这也是我喜欢写出函数表达式的原因之一
And it's also one of the reasons why I like writing out function expressions in
它们的完整形式和
their full form and
嵌套而不是试图将所有内容串在一行上。
nested rather than trying to string everything together on one line.
我喜欢看到功能边界，我喜欢在心理上处理
Is I like to see the function boundaries and I like to mentally process
每个示波器周围基本上都有一个气泡。
that there's essentially a bubble around each of these scopes.
在Ask周围有一个泡泡，在其他班级周围有一个泡泡，然后是一个泡泡
There's a bubble around ask, and a bubble around other class, and then a bubble
围绕全局范围，并且这些气泡严格嵌套在彼此内部。
around the global scope, and these bubbles are strictly nested inside of each other.
所以他们不会越界。
So it's not like they're gonna cross the line.
不是说我们会有一个部分在两个父作用域中的作用域，
It's not like we're gonna have one scope that's partially in two parent scopes,
它们完全包含在彼此内部。
they're entirely contained within each other.
事实上，在气泡内部观察这些范围，
As a matter of fact, visualizing these scopes inside of the bubbles,
虽然这是我更喜欢的思考方式。
while it's kind of my preferred way of thinking about it.
有另一种可视化的方法是足够有效的
There's another way of visualizing this that is effective enough that it
实际上可以出现在你的编辑器中。
can actually show up inside of your editor.
在我的编辑器中，我使用sublime，我想我之前已经提到过。
In my editor I use sublime, I think I've mentioned before.
在我的编辑器中，我有一个可以打开模式的插件。
In my editor, I have a plugin that I can switch on a mode.
它使用了一种名为ES Level的工具，这是一种分析
It uses a tool called ES levels, which is a tool that analyzes
基本上所有水桶和大理石所在的范围级别。
the scope levels of where basically all your buckets and marbles are.
这就是当我拿到同样的一段代码时的样子
And this is what it looks like when I take that same piece of code and
我在我的编辑器里面打开它。
I turn it on inside of my editor.
您会注意到它正在给不同的变量引用着色，并且
You'll notice that it is coloring the different variable references and
根据它们所属的范围来确定不同的代码片段。
the different pieces of code according to what scope they belong to.
它基本上是给你的水桶颜色和大理石颜色。
It's basically giving you your bucket colors and your marble colors.
在第7行，您会注意到引用了一种颜色
And you'll notice down on line 7 that there's a color being referenced for
老师，它与第4行中的那个相匹配。
teacher and that matches the one from line 4.
&gt；&gt；[INAUDIBLE]&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以，
&gt;&gt; [INAUDIBLE] &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So again,
这是一个叫做ES级别的插件。
this is a plugin that's called ES levels.
现在，它不是完美的，它确实有一些怪癖。
Now, it is not perfect, it does have some quirks to it.
如果您注意到这个特定示例，其中我有一个名称函数表达式，
If you notice this particular example, where I have a name function expression,
还记得我们讨论过的函数表达式的名称吗？
remember what we talked about with the names of function expressions?
这些名称应该放在它们的封闭范围内。
Those names are supposed to go inside of their enclosing scope.
那么，为什么第1行上的foo被涂上了颜色，就好像它在外部范围中一样？
So why is that foo on line 1 colored as if it is in the outer scope?
如果它是一个函数声明，它会这样做，但在这里，他们这样做是为了
It would if it was a function declaration, but here they're doing that for
函数表达式。
a function expression.
几年前我向ES级的项目报告了这一点，
Years ago I reported this to the ES level's project,
并说这是一个应该上色的bug，就好像它属于这个范围一样。
and said this is a bug that should be colored as if it belongs to the scope.
他们做得很好，事实上，
And they did a whole bunch of well, actuallys on,
从技术上讲，该名称在其自己的中间范围内。
technically that name is in its own intermediate scope.
所以给它同样的颜色也是正确的，而且
And so it would even be right to give it the same colors, and
然后他们进行了一个又大又长的事情。
then they went on this big long thing.
他们会说如果我们用真正的方法，我们会有太多的颜色，所以
And they'd say we'd have too many colors if we did it the real way, so
我们就不管它了，我们就把它弄坏了。
we're just gonna leave it alone, we're just gonna leave it broken.
所以它并不完美，但有时能看到哪里是非常有帮助的
So it's not perfect, but it is super helpful at times to be able to see where
这些变量是来自，还是为什么我被这些变量弄得如此困惑？
are these variables coming from, or why am I getting so confused by these variables?
所以我会把那个插件翻进去。
So I'll flip that plugin in.
但我喜欢可视化我的范围边界的想法。
But I like the idea of visualizing my scope boundaries.
它帮助我保持所有词法范围的直接性。
It helps me keep all of the lexical scopes straight.